Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Administrative files
  - Senior staff files
    - Anderson, Jack (John) files, Deputy of Programs
      - Julius Cohen, Syracuse University, Division of Special Education and Rehabilation, 1965 (Box 84)
      - Legal services, 1967; 2 folders (Box 84)
      - Library, 1966-1967 (Box 84)
      - Library to order, 1966 (Box 84)
      - Management Information System, 1967 (Box 84)
      - Manpower Opportunity Adult Basic Education, 1967 (Box 84)
      - Manpower Opportunity Adult Education programs, 1967 (Box 85)
      - Maps (documents), 1966 (Box 85)
      - Material from HEW on employed mothers, 1966 (Box 85)
      - Memos, incoming, May1966-Nov 1966 (Box 85)
      - Memos, outgoing, Sep 1966 - Feb 1967 (Box 85)
      - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 85)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 85)
      - Mobile classroom, 1966-1967 (Box 85)
      - Model cities, 1966 (Box 85)
      - Monthly report draft, 1965 (Box 85)
      - Monthly reports, 1967 (Box 85)
      - Monthly reports, 1967; 2 folders (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood Action Group Society, day care proposal, Ana Thompson, 1966 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood board elections, 1966; 2 folders (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood board training, 1967 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood board, miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood boards, general, 1966 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood center committees, 1967 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood Centers, personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood committees, 1967 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood elections, 1966 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood health services proposal, 1966 (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1967; 2 folders (Box 86)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps proposals, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 87)
      - New assignment, 1966 (Box 87)
      - New building, 1966 (Box 87)
      - New proposals III, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Nominee's meeting, 1965 (Box 87)
      - OEO, 1967 (Box 87)
      - OEO CAP 20, 1967 (Box 87)
      - OEO evaluation team, 1967 (Box 87)
      - OEO report data, 1965 (Box 87)
      - OEO statistical reports, 1966-1967 (Box 87)
      - OMAT, 1967 (Box 87)
      - OMAT monthly reports, 1964-1965 (Box 87)
      - Onondaga County, 1966-1967 (Box 87)
      - Onondaga County Boy Scouts of America, 1966 (Box 87)
      - Onondaga County organizations, 1967 (Box 87)
      - Onondaga Neighborhood Legal Services, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 87)
      - Onondaga Neighborhood Legal Services, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 88)
      - On-the-job training, 1967 (Box 88)
      - Original (handwritten) agendas and budgets, Mar 1967 (Box 88)
      - Original (handwritten) agendas, budgets, and memos, Mar-Jun 1967 (Box 88)
      - Originals (handwritten) correspondence and memos, Sep 1966 - Mar 1967; 7 folders (Box 88)
      - Outline for proposed training program, Dr. Bettye Caldwell, undated (Box 89)
      - Penn program, 1965 (Box 89)
      - Performing arts, 1966 (Box 89)
      - Personal letters, 1966 (Box 89)
      - Personnel (general), 1966-1967 (Box 89)
      - Personnel policy, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Personnel, education, 1966-1967 (Box 89)
      - Pre-employment, 1967 (Box 89)
      - Pre-vocational rating, 1966 (Box 89)
      - Priorities meeting, 1966 (Box 89)
      - Program coordinating committee, 1967 (Box 89)
      - Program coordination, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Program development, 1965-1966; 3 folders (Box 89)
      - Program development correspondence, 1967 (Box 89)
      - Program development personnel, 1967 (Box 89)
      - Program directors, 1964 (Box 89)
      - Program staff design, undated (Box 89)
      - Project Head Start conference, 1967; 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Public affairs, 1966-1967 (Box 90)
      - Recreation contract, 1965 (Box 90)
      - Refunding, 1967; 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Refunding, 1967; 3 folders (Box 90)
      - Refunding administration, research, training, CMDC, 1967 (Box 90)
      - Refunding application, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 90)
      - Refunding board, 1967 (Box 90)
      - Refunding day care, 1966-1967 (Box 90)
      - Refunding day care, 1966-1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding education, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding Head Start, 1966-1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding information and referral, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding information and referral, 1967; 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Refunding legal services, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding matching funds, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding neighborhood based, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Refunding priorities committee, 1967 (Box 91)
      - Rehabiliation program, 1965 (Box 91)
      - Report of the Joint Neighborhood Writing committee, draft, undated (Box 91)
      - Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 91)
      - Reproduced materials, 1966; 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Requisitions, 1966-1967 (Box 91)
      - Requisitions, regular programs, 1967 (Box 92)
      - Research, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Research and demonstration, 1967 (Box 92)
      - Research department, personnel, 1966-1967 (Box 92)
      - Reservations (airlines), undated (Box 92)
      - The role of the neighborhood worker in CFO, 1965 (Box 92)
      - Rural opportunities, 1967 (Box 92)
      - School social workers report, Jul 1965 (Box 92)
      - Senior staff, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Senior staff memo regarding redefinition of the role of Program Specialists and Field Operations personnel, 1966 (Box 92)
      - Seymour Street center, 1967 (Box 92)
      - Small Business Administration, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Small Business Development Center, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Special summer programs, 1967 (Box 92)
      - Staff committee for non-professional training, 1965 (Box 92)
      - Staff lists, 1965 (Box 92)
      - Staff minutes to write, 1965 (Box 92)
      - State Youth Division, 1965 (Box 92)
      - Statistical reports, 1967 (Box 92)
      - Strategies and suggestions for training nonprofessionals, by Frank Reissman, 1965 (Box 92)
      - Summer program, 11 folders
        - Application, 1967 (Box 93)
        - Campership, 1967 (Box 93)
        - Central, 1967 (Box 93)
        - Central, 1967 (Box 93)
        - East Side, 1967 (Box 93)
        - North Side, 1967 (Box 93)
        - Personnel, 1967 (Box 93)
        - Refunding, 1966-1967 (Box 93)
        - Tallman, 1967 (Box 93)
        - West Side, 1967 (Box 93)
      - Summer recreation, 1965 (Box 93)
      - Summer tutorial program, 1967 (Box 93)
      - Syracuse as a demonstration city, history, 1966 (Box 93)
      - Syracuse neighborhood survey, undated; 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Syracuse University, 1965 (Box 93)
      - Task force, 1965 (Box 93)
      - Title I, 1967 (Box 93)
      - Title V, 1965 (Box 93)
      - Title V proposal, 1967 (Box 94)
      - Top Cat, 1966-1967 (Box 94)
      - Training, 1966 (Box 94)
      - Training, 1967; 3 folders (Box 94)
      - Training material, 1966 (Box 94)
      - Training probation, undated (Box 94)
      - Training program advisory committee, 1964 (Box 94)
      - Training program general, 1963-1964 (Box 94)
      - Training program staff, 1964 (Box 94)
      - Training program teachers, 1964 (Box 95)
      - Tuturial program, 1967 (Box 95)
      - Unmarried Mothers, restorative services subcommittee, 1965 (Box 95)
      - Versatile funding, 1967 (Box 95)
      - VISTA, 1965 (Box 95)
      - VISTAS trainees, 1965 (Box 95)
      - Volunteers, 1964 (Box 95)
      - Voter registration, door-to-door kit, 1964 (Box 356)
      - Welfare, 1967 (Box 95)
      - Welfare training, 1963 (Box 95)
      - West Side mobile classroom, 1967 (Box 95)
      - William Burton letters, 1967 (Box 95)
      - William Burton memo, 1967 (Box 95)
      - Working file [correspondence and memos], 1967 (Box 95)
      - Working file [correspondence, memos, and minutes], 1966 (Box 95)
      - Yeshiva University (work study assignments), 1966 (Box 95)
      - Youth services, 1966-1967 (Box 95)
    - Baer, Betty files, See Neighborhood Centers: Staff files: Baer, Betty files
    - Biographical sketches
      - Abe Bolgatz, 1965 (Box 95)
      - Alfred R Seigle, 1963-1966 (Box 95)
      - Bessie Manuel, 1966 (Box 95)
      - Board of Directors, 1964-1965 (Box 95)
      - Charles Jorgenson, 1967 (Box 96)
      - Dr Franklyn S Barry, 1963 (Box 96)
      - Emil Hale, 1967 (Box 96)
      - George Silcott, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Gerald Stern, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Harry S Balmer, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Irving G Berman, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Jean Reeves, 1963-1964 (Box 96)
      - John F Flanagan, 1965 (Box 96)
      - John Murray, 1966 (Box 96)
      - Joseph John Centrone, 1966 (Box 96)
      - Minna Buck, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Raymond C Gantter, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Senior staff, 1966-1967 (Box 96)
      - S. William Dwyer, 1967 (Box 96)
    - Buck, Minna files, Executive Assistant
      - Budget, education, 1965 (Box 96)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966; 10 folders (Box 96)
      - Correspondence, 1966; 4 folders (Box 97)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1966; 3 folders (Box 97)
      - Employment service, US project cause, 1966
      - Memos, 1965-1967 (Box 97)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965; 2 folders (Box 97)
      - Monthly report, 1966 (Box 97)
      - Monthly report (staff), 1966 (Box 97)
      - Onondaga County Welfare Department, 1965-1967 (Box 97)
    - Davis, John files, See Public Affairs: Staff files: Davis, John files
    - Ise, Moko files, See Research files: Staff files: Ise, Moko
    - Jorgensen, Charles files, Deputy of Administration
      - Community Action memo, 1967 (Box 97)
      - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 97)
      - Correspondence and memos, 1967; 4 folders (Box 97)
      - Kiplinger letter, 1967 (Box 98)
      - Manpower sources, correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 98)
      - Memos, 1966-1967 (Box 98)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity correspondence, 1967 (Box 98)
    - Meetings and memos
      - Executive staff meeting minutes, 1965 (Box 98)
      - Executive and senior staff meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 98)
      - Memos, 1965-1966; 5 folders (Box 98)
      - Memos and meetings, 1967; 2 folders
      - Senior staff meeting agendas, 1967 (Box 98)
      - Senior staff meeting minutes, 1965-1967; 4 folders (Box 98)
      - Senior staff meetings notes, 1967; 2 folders (Box 98)
      - Senior staff memos and meetings, 1967 (Box 98)
      - Senior staff memos and meetings, 1967 (Box 99)
      - Staff meeting minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 99)
      - Staff meetings, 1965 (Box 99)
      - Staff orientation, 1966 (Box 99)
    - Murray, John files, See Financial files: Staff files: Murray, John files
    - Rosenfeld, Hilda files, See Research files: Staff files: Rosenfeld, Hilda files
    - Smith, Bill files, Personnel Director, Field Operations Director
      - Action area, county, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Administrative procedure, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Agenda committee, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Alphabet game, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Authorized signatures, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Bernard Shell correspondence, 1967 (Box 99)
      - Bi-monthly report, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Boy Scouts, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Budget correspondence, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Budget memorandum, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Business office, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Business procedures, 1966 (Box 99)
      - CAP memorandum, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Chamber of Commerce and Manufacturer's Association, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Charge sheets, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Clambake, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Clerical in-service training session, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Clerical staff, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Combined budget for neighborhood centers, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Community Action Training Center, 1965 (Box 99)
      - Community service, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Constitution of POWER, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Consultant, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Consultant expense, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Consumable supplies, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Consumer survey, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Continuing Education for the Public Welfare, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Coordinators and campaign managers, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Corporate membership, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Council of Churches, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Crusade history, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Cultural enrichment trips, 1966 (Box 99)
      - CUNA International, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Duplicating, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Eastwood homes, NESPO, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Economic Opportunity Act, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Education correspondence, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Effective conference leadership, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Election budget, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Election supplies, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Election, Tallman, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Elections, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Elections, West Side, 1966 (Box 99)
      - ELKS marching band, 1966 (Box 99)
      - Employment advisory committee, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment committee meeting, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment correspondence, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment manpower, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment supervisors committee, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment task force, undated (Box 100)
      - Employment task force sub-committee minutes, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment training correspondence, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Employment work order, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Equipment, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Equipment list, Onondaga reservation, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Equipment, West Side Center, 1966 (Box 100)
      - ESEA, 1965 (Box 100)
      - Evaluation forms, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Evaluation reports, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Evaluations, general, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Field operations center staff, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Field operations director, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Field operations legal services and court cases, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Field operations, maintenance, 1966 (Box 100)
      - GSA vehicles, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Guidelines, CFO, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Haryou-Act, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Holidays, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Housing, general information, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Identification card, designing of, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Indian reservation, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Information, 1967 (Box 100)
      - Information sessions, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Information summaries, 1966 (Box 100)
      - In-service training, general, 1966 (Box 100)
      - In-service training, meeting, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Insurance centers, undated (Box 100)
      - Internal staff use only, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Job descriptions, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Job orders, 1966-1967 (Box 100)
      - Joint information and referred committee, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Joint neighborhood board meeting, 1965 (Box 100)
      - Joint neighborhood board planning committee, in-service training, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Joint neighborhood workers committee meeting, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Joint nominating committee, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Juvenile Probation department, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Leadership laboratory, 1966-1967 (Box 100)
      - Lease East Side Center, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Leased housing, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Low income male program inclusion, 1966 (Box 100)
      - Maintenance, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Manpower correspondence, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Manpower staff organization, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Meeting schedule, revision, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Meeting, weekly schedule, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Memos, 1967 (Box 101)
      - Mileage allowance, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Ministers, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Minutes and mailing, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Minutes formats, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 101)
      - Miscellaneous information, undated (Box 101)
      - Monthly report format, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Monthly report, memos, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Monthly reports (Box 101)
      - Moving expenses, 1966 (Box 101)
      - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood board areas, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood board correspondence, 1965 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood board, general, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood centers open house, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood self-help committee, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Neighborhood service centers, division of welfare, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Newspapers, 1966 (Box 102)
      - New York State employment service, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Onondaga Department of Public Welfare, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Onondaga reservation, undated (Box 102)
      - Open house, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Organization boards, undated (Box 102)
      - Orientation to youth problems, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Pamphlets, 1965-1966 (Box 102)
      - Parking problems, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Peace Corps neighborhood work project, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Pioneer Center, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Pre-employment Manpower program memo, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Pre-employment program, undated (Box 102)
      - Procedures for work orders, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Program coordinators, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Program development, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Program operations, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Program participants, undated (Box 102)
      - Program specialist, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Program staff training project, undated (Box 102)
      - Project Steering Committee of the Syracuse Council of Methodist Churches, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Proposed workshop, undated (Box 102)
      - Public information, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Purchasing, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Recording of minutes, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Recruiting folder, 1967 (Box 102)
      - Recruitment and referral procedure, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Rent contract - West Side Center, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Resumes, 1965 (Box 102)
      - Routing slips, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Salaries, clerical, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Salary adjustments, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Salary advances, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Schedule, 1966-1967 (Box 102)
      - Scholarships, 1967 (Box 102)
      - SCM Corporation, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Secretarial pool - job performance, 1967 (Box 102)
      - Seminar, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Senior staff correspondence, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Senior staff meeting conference room, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Senior staff personnel - Manpower, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Senior staff seminar and general staff meeting, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Seymour Street center, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Shriver memo, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Signature authorization, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Speakers and consultants, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Speakers Bureau, information sheet, undated (Box 102)
      - Special study center report, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Special summer programs, undated (Box 102)
      - Staff appointments, 1966 (Box 102)
      - Staff evaluation chart, undated (Box 102)
      - Staff minutes, 1965 (Box 102)
      - Staff party, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Staff resignations, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Staff salaries, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Staffing patterns, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Structural changes, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Structure, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Study Center program, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Substitute mothers, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Summer Head Start program, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Summer recreation, 1965 (Box 103)
      - Surplus food, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Syracuse Community Nursey, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Syracuse Housing Authority, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Syracuse Manpower Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman Base, undated (Box 103)
      - Tallman Board meeting, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman Center monthly report, 1967 (Box 103)
      - Tallman correspondence, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman job performance, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman Neighborhood Board, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman New York trip, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman program particpation, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tallman Teen Council, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Tardiness and absenteeism, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Task Force, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Teacher Aides, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Team meeting - East Side Center, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Teen Council budget centers, 1965-1966 (Box 103)
      - Teen Council East Side, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Telephone lists, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Television channel 24, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Termination, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Time cards, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Time off, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Traffic violations, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Training material, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Transportation, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Union-Sarah Center, 1966 (Box 103)
      - United Community Chest and Council of Onondaga, Inc., 1966 (Box 103)
      - Urban renewal, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Vacation time, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Vouchers, 1966 (Box 103)
      - WCNY-TV, staff meeting, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Welfare allowances, 1966 (Box 103)
      - West Richmond day camps, 1966 (Box 103)
      - West Side Center - general, 1966 (Box 103)
      - West Side Center, education committee, 1966 (Box 103)
      - West Side Joint Education representatives, 1966 (Box 103)
      - West Side neighborhood board, 1966 (Box 103)
      - West Side publicity, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Working papers, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Youth program, 1966 (Box 103)
      - Youth specialist, 1966 (Box 103)
- Neighborhood Centers
  - East Side Center
    - Adult program, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Advisory committee, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Advisory council (to become Neighborhood Board), 1964 (Box 104)
    - Annual reports, undated (Box 104)
    - Barber association committee, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Beauticians meetings minutes, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Board correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 104)
    - Budget, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Budget advisory committee, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Building committee, 1966 (Box 104)
    - By-laws committee, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Change of address, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Cleaning function, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Committees of the board, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Consumer reports, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Consumer survey, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Cooking class, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, 1967; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Day care committee, 1966-1967 (Box 104)
    - Easter week bus trips, 1965 (Box 104)
    - Education committee, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Education staff, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Elections, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Employment committee, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Equipment, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Fact sheet, 1966; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Field trips, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Guitar class, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Head Start committee, summer program, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Hot lunch committee (summer program), 1967 (Box 104)
    - Housing committee, 1967 (Box 104)
    - In-service training, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Job orders for copies, 1967; 4 folders (Box 104)
    - Joint legal resource committee, 1966; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Mailing lists, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Maintenance, 1967; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Monthly reports, 1966-1967 (Box 104)
    - Morning reports, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Neighborhood board, 1966; 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood board elections, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood board meeting minutes, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood board meetings, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood board memos and correspondence, 1967 (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood board minutes, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood center, 1967; 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Neighborhood study center, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Nominating committee, 1966-1967 (Box 105)
    - Oakwood babysitting center, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Oakwood center, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Open house invitation list, 1965 (Box 105)
    - Open house invitations, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Personnel, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Personnel, memorandums, 1966-1967 (Box 105)
    - Planning committee, 1967 (Box 105)
    - Pre-employment, 1967 (Box 105)
    - Preschool, 1967 (Box 105)
    - Program coordinator, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Programs operative, 1967 (Box 105)
    - Proposed expenditures, 1966 (Box 105)
    - Publicity committee, undated (Box 105)